那么现在我们创建了一个简单的服务
So now we have a simple service.
简不简单？
Wasn't that easy?
但是它仍然不能自己唤醒自己
But it still doesn't wake itself up.
幸运的是，android的一个系统服务可以完成这个功能
Fortunately, there's
a system service for that.
现在可以介绍一下alarm manager
This is a good opportunity to
introduce the alarm manager.
Alarm Manager允许你通知系统
The alarm manager allows you to
tell the system that you want it to
在过一段时间后启动你应用程序的某个组件
wake a component of your application
up after a period of time and
并在后台进行一些处理操作
do some processing in the background.
你甚至可以通过它隔一段时间唤醒你的应用程序
You can even have it wake up your
application periodically, but
那么我们在后台唤醒了什么呢？
what do we wake up in the background?
它是我们之前没接触过的一个Android组件，
That would be an Android
component we haven't seen before,
叫做Broadcast Receiver(广播接收)
called a broadcast receiver.
Broadcast Receiver是专门用来接收Intent广播的类
A broadcast receiver is a special
class that is used to receive
这些广播常常来自于其他应用程序
intent broadcasts,
often from other applications.
通常，Broadcast Receiver会设置一个IntentFilter
Typically, a broadcast receiver
will register an intent filter for
来过滤所接收的广播
these broadcasts.
这也是应用程序监听警告提醒的一种方法
It's also one way the application
will listen in on alarms.
警告提醒利用另外一种Intent，叫做PendingIntent
Alarms take advantage of a new kind
of intent, called a PendingIntent.
PendingIntent是一种特殊的Intent
A PendingIntent is
a special kind of intent
它从一个应用程序传递到另一个应用程序
that is handed from one
application to another.
PendingIntent和普通Intent最大的不同在于
The big difference between
a PendingIntent and a regular intent
PendingIntent允许程序利用与该intent相关的权限和
is that a PendingIntent gives permission
for the app using it to send data with
程序标识来发送数据。
the same permissions and application
identity as the app that created it.
在Android中，系统进程可以通过它从后台异步
In Android this allows the system
process to call your application back
调用你的应用程序而不用遵循Android安全模型
in a specific asynchronous way without
compromising the Android security model.
在警告信息中，PendingIntent是在AlarmManager中被用来
In alarms a pending intent
is used by the alarm manager
和我们所创建的BroadcastReceiver进行交互用的
to talk to the broadcast
receiver we create.
下面我们来添加一些警告相关的东东。
Let's add some alarm stuff.
首先，我们在SunshineService中添加一个
First, I'm going to add
a BroadcastReceiver as a static inner
内部静态类，它继承BroadcastReceiver。
class of SunshineService.
因为它是Android组件，
Since this is an Android component,
所以需要在Manifest文件中进行注册。
I'll register this broadcast
receiver in the manifest.
注意内部静态类的表示方法
Note the way a static
inner class is notated.
Okay
Okay.
我这里已经给出了BroadcastReceiver处理警告的基本框架
I've given you the bones of a broadcast
receiver that can handle an alarm.
接下来就该轮你了
But now it's your turn.
你可以通过显式Intent来创建一个PendingIntent
You can create a PendingIntent
from an explicit intent
用它通过alarm manager来激活你的BroadcastReceiver
to have the alarm manager
activate your broadcast receiver.
我建议你把警报间隔设置短点
I recommend setting the alarm
to something absurdly short,
比如5秒，这样你就能看出它的效果了
like five seconds, so
you can easily test that it's working.